{
  "Computer": [
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "What invention replaced vacuum tubes and made computers much smaller and faster.",
      "back": "transistor"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "What name is given to half of a Byte (4 bits)?",
      "back": "Nibble"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "The initials GUI stand for Graphical User Interface",
      "front": "The initials GUI stand for ...",
      "back": "Graphical User Interface"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "What does ICMP stand for?",
      "back": "Internet Control Message Protocol"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "In what year was the Domain Name System created?",
      "back": "1983"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "What company invented the floppy disk?",
      "back": "IBM"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "Tux is teh name of Linux's Mascot",
      "front": "... is teh name of Linux's Mascot",
      "back": "Tux"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "In what year was the first Apple computer released?",
      "back": "1976"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "The headquarters of Microsoft is located in what US State?",
      "back": "Washington"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "Netscape Navigator was originaly named Mozilla.",
      "front": "Netscape Navigator was originaly named ....",
      "back": "Mozilla"
    }
  ],
  "History": [
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "front": "The Great Pyramid of ... is located in Cairo, Egypt.",
      "back": "Giza"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "The 13th constitutional Amendment banned slavery.",
      "front": "The ... constitutional Amendment banned slavery.",
      "back": "13th"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "John F. Kennedy was assasinated in what US city?",
      "back": "Dallas"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "American involvement in the Korean War took place in the 1950's.",
      "front": "American involvement in the ... War took place in the 1950's.",
      "back": "Korean"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "The Magna Carta was published by the King of England.",
      "front": "The Magna Carta was published by the King of ....",
      "back": "England"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "Johannes Gutenburg is famous for developing the first printing press.",
      "front": "Johannes Gutenburg is famous for developing the first ....",
      "back": "printing press"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "The Hundred Years War was fought between England and what other country?",
      "back": "France"
    },
    {
      "type": "basic",
      "front": "What Romain Emperor built a massive wall across Norther Britain in 122 A.D.?",
      "back": "Hadrian"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "Martin Luther wrote a document known as the 95 Theses.",
      "front": "... wrote a document known as the 95 Theses.",
      "back": "Martin Luther"
    },
    {
      "type": "cloze",
      "full": "The Khmer Rouge was a regime ruling Cambodia in the 20th century.",
      "front": "The Khmer Rouge was a regime ruling ... in the 20th century.",
      "back": "Cambodia"
    }
  ]
}